Marlon Riggs Papers, 1957-1994 M1759
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Audio Visual
  - Subseries 9: Other Video Projects
    - Riggs, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 4)
      Riggs #7 and #8
    - Film Festival, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 15mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 5)
      Riggs and Wendell Harris at Denver Int'l Film Festival on 07 Nov 1991
    - Malcolm X, 1992; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 6)
      Riggs and Ron Simmons - On Malcolm (from 30 Apr 1992)
    - KGO tape, 1987; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 7)
      Riggs on KGO on 08 Feb 1987
    - KGO tape, 1987; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 30mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 8)
      Riggs on KGO-AM Carolyn Craven Show on 08 Feb 1987
    - Riggs Interview, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 9)
      Reel Talk #27 - Wendy Braitman interviews Riggs and Nettie Wild
    - Riggs Interview, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 10)
      Riggs Fresh Air Interview on 11 Jul 1991
    - Riggs Interview, 1990; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 11)
      Dialogue - Riggs on KMEL-FM on 22 Apr 1990
    - Riggs Interview, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 12mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 12)
      Riggs interviewed by Robin Donahue
    - Why We Love Marlon, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 110mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 13)
      Why we love Marlon
    - Riggs Interview, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 120mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 14)
      Riggs Interviews - from 09 and 10 Jul 1991
    - Riggs Interview, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 120mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 15)
      Riggs Interviews - from 10 Jul 1991
    - Riggs Interview, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 16)
      Riggs Interviews - from 11 Jul 1991
    - Riggs Interview, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 120mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 17)
      Riggs Interviews - from 12 Jul 1991
    - Riggs Interview, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 120mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 18)
      Riggs Interviews - from 16 Jul 1991
    - Riggs Interview, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 120mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 19)
      Riggs Interviews - from 25 Jul 1991
    - Berkeley, 1987; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 20)
      Riggs at Wheeler Hall UC, Berkeley on 12 Feb 1987
    - Interviews, 1988; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 21)
      NYC 07 Aug 1988 Jesse Harris, City Hall: Homeless
    - Ida Jackson, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 22)
      Ida Jackson I and II, #5 and #6
    - Ida Jackson, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 23)
      Ida Jackson #7, 8, 9 and 10
    - Reggie Jackson, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 24)
      Reggie Jackson, Gordon Chambers
    - Interviews, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 25)
      Tape of Barbara Chin, Colin Robinson and Renee McCoy
    - Interviews, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 26)
      Interview tapes - storage?
    - Harvard, 1990; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 27)
      Harvard speech - 27 Oct 1990
    - St Croix, 1992; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 28)
      St Croix 30 Mar 1992
    - Readings, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 29)
      Lawrence Crouchett, Dramatic Reading, Ida L. Jackson (Scratch Dellums)
    - VTT, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 30)
      V.T.T. Premiere - Lawrence Crouchett, Dramatic Reading, Ida L. Jackson (Scratch Dellums)
    - Kenny Hall, 1990; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 31)
      Kenny Hall 08 Jan 1990 pt 1 and 2
    - Kenny Hall, 1990; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 32)
      Kenny Hall 08 Jan 1990 pt 3 and 4
    - Bill Moyers, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 33)
      Recovery Group with Bill Moyers (PBS television program 'Circle of Recovery' 1991)
    - Recovery, 1990; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 34)
      Recovery first shoot- 07 Jan 1990
    - Reconstruction, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 35)
      Reconstruction - Side 1
    - Clark & Co, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 36)
      Clark & Co - (radio show from WIS Public Radio, Wisconsin - 11 Jul 1991, 7-8am)
    - Alan Miller, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 37)
      Alan Miller
    - Len, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 120mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 38)
      Kate's conversation with Len on 17 Dec 1991
    - Stimmerman, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 23, Folder 39)
      Dan Stimmerman
    - Answermachine, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 23, Folder 40)
      Answermachine tape
    - Donahue, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 41)
      Donahue - Black Women Writers
    - Welsing, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 23, Folder 42)
      Dr Frances Cress Welsing
    - Conference, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 1)
      Black Popular Culture Conference, Day 1, 06 Dec 1991 (Marlon Riggs spoke at this conference, along with Cornel West and Henry Gates)
    - Conference, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; (Flat-box 24, Folder 2)
      Black Popular Culture Conference, Day 1, 06 Dec 1991
    - Conference, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 3)
      Black Popular Culture Conference, Day 2, 07 Dec 1991
    - Conference, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 4)
    - Censorship, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 5)
      Silent Scissors: A Look at censorship in the Broadcast Media - 24 Jul 1991 (includes clips used from Tongues Untied)
    - Speech, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 6)
      Newton Minov - Vast Wasteland Speech (09 May 1961)
    - AIVF, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 7)
      AIVF (Association of Independent Video and Filmmakers) - 'Does Radical Content require Radical Form?' from the N.Y. Lesbian and Gay Experimental Film Festival - 2 tapes
    - AIVF, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 8)
      AIVF (Association of Independent Video and Filmmakers) -'Race and Representation in Britain/USA' - 2 tapes
    - NEA Speech, 1992; Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 9)
      National Press Club Library - John Frohnmayer (Chairman of the NEA) speaks - 23 Mar 1992
    - Black Eyes, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 10)
      Black Eyes Production - Black Women in Recovery - Sides C and D
    - MLK, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 11)
      The Great March to Freedom - Rev. Martin Luther King, Detroit, June 23, 1963
    - Civil Rights, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 12)
      Voices of the Civil Rights movement
    - Music, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 40mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 13)
      Mary Watkins 'SpiritSong' Solo Piano compositions
    - Music, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 14)
      Steve Langley - SteveSongs Vol.11
    - Music, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 30mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 15)
      3 songs of Gwen Avery
    - Music, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 22mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 16)
      Mark Pierson - 5 works - Music for synth Sax Percussion
    - Eric Perez, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 46mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 17)
      Tape for Riggs
    - Alex Langford, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 18)
      Hey Lover
    - Eldoradio, 1990; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 19)
      18 Feb 1990 - interview with Riggs and Philip Roth by a german Interviewer from Berlin Film festival
    - Passages Passanter, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 20)
      26 Nov 1991 (possibly either dutch poetry or dutch radio)
    - MR - TV, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 21)
      MR - TV? NBGTL conference?
    - MR - TV, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 22)
      MR - TV?
    - Phone Message tape, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 23)
      message for callers to the Ethnic Notions office number
    - Phone Message tape, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 24)
      messages left for Riggs on an answermachine
    - Dictation, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 25)
      Dictation from 14 Jan 1991
    - Music, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 26)
      North Carolina Minstrels
    - Music, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 27)
      Blues for Mister Charlie - Bobby Sharp
    - Music, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 28)
      Miriam Makeba 'Sangoma'
    - Music, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 94mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 30)
      AC-DC Blues/Gay Jazz/Sissy mans Blues/Copulatin Blues
    - Music, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 31)
      Higher Ground: Songs of Love and Freedom
    - Conference, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 32)
      Audio of conference? Bell hooks speaking
    - Conference, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 33)
      Conference? Panelists on Black Film - including Marlon
    - Conference, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 34)
      Black Popular Culture Conference
    - Conference, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 24, Folder 35)
    - Black History Month, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 36)
      Arts Spectrum, Black History Month, Black Women Writers - Barbara Christian interviewed
    - Riggs Phone Call, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 37)
      mostly blank but one section has Marlon on phone speaking his own number, which is repeated back to him by the person on the other end
    - Photographic Negs (Box 54, Folder 4)
      1957 Prayer Pilgrammage for Freedom
    - Photographic Negs (Box 54, Folder 5)
      Photos from the NGBL Conference in LA
    - Slides, Photographic slides (Box 96)
      Photographic slides from exhibition (Exhibition slides No.s 1-285), also some Ethnic Notions slides and titles from Changing Images project
    - Marlon reporting, 1981; Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 5mins (Box 174, Folder 1)
      Audio of Riggs reporting on 2 news items for CNS news (n.d.)
    - Prayer Pilgrimage for Freedom 1957, Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 1200ft (Box 174, Folder 2)
      Audio of a WLIB radio broadcast from 18 May 1957 of the Prayer Pilgrimage for Freedom demonstartion in Washington
    - NY Illustrated program/March on Washington, Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 1200ft (Box 174, Folder 3)
      Audio of a WNBC Television broadcast program about Andrew Goodman, broadcast on Sat. 07 Nov 1984, also portions the March on Washington on 28 Aug 1963 broadcast on WLIB NY radio on 29 Aug 1963
      - Songs of Freedom/The American Revolution, Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 1200ft (Box 174, Folder 5)
        Audio recording of a television broadcast of the program 'Songs of Freedom' featuring the Freedom singers and songs by Bob Dylan and Odetta, broadcast on 01 Sept 1963 on Chanel 5 TV, also includes the program 'Crucial Summer' examining the Civil Rights Bill and a CBS News item at end of tape featuring news about disturbances in Plaquermine Louisiana - side 2 features an audio recording of the NBC television program 'The American Revolution of '63'
    - My Childhood, Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 1200ft (Box 174, Folder 4)
      Audio of a television broadcast on WNEW-TV on 01 Jun 1964 featuring the remembered childhoods of Hubert Humphrey and James Baldwin
    - The American Revolution, Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 1200ft (Box 174, Folder 6)
      Audio recording of the NBC television program 'The American Revolution of '63' about the history of the civil rights movement and featuring statements by Civil Rights leaders and freedom workers, broadcast on NBC on 02 Sep 1963
    - Tribute - Tape 1 - 8mm transfer, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 199, Folder 1)
      Includes promo Afro Homes, Alan Miller, David Kirkland, Blackberri, The Office with Marlon and Vivian and Ed Rudolph
    - Tribute - Tape 2 - 8mm transfer, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 199, Folder 2)
      Includes Jack, Tim Riera, Andrew Stern and Joan, Reggie and Al Cunningham
    - Tribute - Tape 3, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 199, Folder 3)
      Includes Nancy and Mark, Marlon footage, Essex and Ben Bagdickean, Debbie Hoffman, Larry and Linda Britt and Vance
    - Tribute - Tape 4, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 199, Folder 4)
      Includes Mary Watkins, Nicole, Karrigan, Rupert, Vince, Mark, Grandmother, Mother, Sasha and Father
    - Tribute - Tape 5, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 199, Folder 5)
      Includes Alex Langford, Rick and Akiba pt1
    - Tribute - Tape 6, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 199, Folder 6)
      Includes Nicole and Akiba pt2, Bob Paris and Janet Jackson
    - Tribute - Tape 7, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 199, Folder 7)
      Includes Badge, Photots and Titles
    - A Tribute to Marlon Riggs, Video: VHS (Box 199, Folder 8)
      A Tribute to Marlon Riggs
    - Miriam Bowdry - 12/9/87 MB-87-19, 1987; Video: VHS; (Box 199, Folder 9)
      Television program with Riggs as guest
    - Changing Images Mirrors of Life Molds of Reality, Video: VHS (Box 199, Folder 10)
      Project that Riggs worked on with others
    - Faces of War, Video: VHS (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Every Child Can and Will Learn, Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 1)
      Fremont Unified School District video made by Scott Video Communications - Version A
    - Facing History: The Black Image in American Art, 1990; Video: VHS; 20mins (Box 200, Folder 2)
      Made by the Brooklyn Museum, April 1990
    - Henry Osawa Tanner, Video: VHS; 20mins (Box 200, Folder 3)
      The Tanner Film Group Video
    - Island of Secret Memories, Video: VHS; 20mins (Box 200, Folder 4)
      Angel Island Revised, Produced by Loni Ding
    - Reflections by Dwight Wilkins, 1991; Video: VHS; 40mins (Box 200, Folder 5)
      16mm submitted on video, 1990
    - Creature Comforts, 1990; Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 6)
      Creature Comforts and Next
    - Relics of Rascism, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Videocopies for Marlon Riggs, 1991; Video: VHS; 40mins (Box 200, Folder 8)
      Directed by Andre Reeder, Amsterdam, Holland, 1991
    - Every Eighteen Minutes, Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Fighting for our lives - facing AIDS in San Francisco, 1987; Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Rough Cut - The Glory and the Power, 1991; Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 200, Folder 11)
      Seg.1 - The Pursuit of Purity, Quest Productions, 1991
    - Private Hungary, Series 1-2, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 12)
      by Peter Forgacs
    - What's L.I.F.E.?, Betty Chisolm Portrait, Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - M.Jackson - Can you remember the time?, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - A View from under the Bridge, 1986; Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 15)
      20mins sample reel, 1986
    - The One Drop Rule, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Color me clean, parts 1 and 2, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - Sin City Diary, Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - PBS: Black History Month presentation, 1987; Video: VHS; 10mins (Box 200, Folder 19)
      Dubbed 12/30/1987
    - Chicano Park, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 200, Folder 20)
      Documentary about a Mexican community park in San Diego
    - The Library of Black History, Video: VHS (Box 200, Folder 21)
      Tony Browns Journal show #617 - 'Black Hollywood, the way it was'
    - Foster Care Panel, 'Take This Heart', Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 22)
    - Danny, 1987; Video: VHS; 20mins (Box 200, Folder 23)
      Stashu Kybartas, 1987
    - National Arts Emergency, 1989; Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 24)
      A video which chronicles the respones of the arts community to the Congressional "attack" on the National Endowment for the Arts' grant-making procedures in 1989.
    - Framing the Panthers in Black and White, Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 25)
      Documentary about the FBI's covert campaign against the Black Panther Party, focusing on the story of one of its leaders, Dhoruba Bin Wahad.
    - Levi Strauss In-Store Video, Video: VHS; 10mins (Box 200, Folder 26)
      Silver Tab instore video sent to Marlon by Aubyn Gwinn, art director at Foote, Cone & Belding, advertising agency - accompanied by a personal note to Marlon from Aubyn
    - Freedom on my Mind, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 27)
      documentary by Connie Field and Marilyn Mulford about the Mississippi freedom movement in the early 1960s
    - In Living Color, 1990; Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 28)
      Episode from 1990
    - For the Love of the Children, 1992; Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 29)
      Concerned Black Men "For the Love of the Children" - Air Date 11 Jul 1992
    - The Ron Reagan Show, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 30)
    - All Our Children (with Bill Moyers), 1991; Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 200, Folder 31)
      1991. Bill Moyers examines the challenges facing America's youth
    - In Living Color, 1991; Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 200, Folder 32)
      Episode from 1991
    - In Living Color, 1992; Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 33)
      Episode from 1992
    - The Cosby Show, 1992; Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 34)
      The last episode of the Cosby Show aired on 30 Apr 1992
    - Boy! What a Girl, 1991; Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 35)
      Various clips including the film 'Boy!What a Girl' (1945), 'Norman, Is that you?' (1976), Arsenio and Fresh Prince (1991)
    - Fear of Disclosure, 1989; Video: VHS; 5mins (Box 200, Folder 36)
      A Short film about disclosing HIV Status to a lover. Produced by Phil Zwickler and David Wojnarowicz, 1989.
    - Corporation with a Movie Camera, Video: VHS; 34mins (Box 200, Folder 37)
      Copy of the film sent by the creator, Joel Katz, with a personal letter to Marlon inclosed with the tape
    - Strange Gifts, 1989; Video: VHS; 5mins (Box 200, Folder 38)
      1989. 'Experimental video in which American "Manifest Destiny" meets its interplanetary counterpart.'
    - Streetfighter in the Courtroom: Charles Garry - Rough Cut #1, Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 39)
      A biography of the life's work of the bay area civil rights lawyer and activist, Charles Garry. Accompanied by a personal note to Marlon from the producer Roxanne Bexjian.
    - Gangs: Dreams Under Fire, 1994; Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 200, Folder 40)
      Tape sent from Marlo Bendau, producer and director of a film examining the causes and consequences of gangs in two different California environments
    - Mi Puerto Rico, 1995; Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 41)
      Documentary through Puerto Rico's rich African, Taino, and Spanish cultural traditions
    - Beasts of Burden, 1992; Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 42)
      A film depicting bike messenger's life and society - tape sent by Wella Lasola, with personal note to Marlon attached
    - Framing Lesbian Fashion, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 200, Folder 43)
      Rough Cut - A documentary by Karen Everett looking at the evolution of fashion trends among America's lesbian population
    - Fighting for Our Lives-Facing AIDS in San Francisco, Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 44)
      Documentary directed by Ellen Siedler about the early days of the AIDS epidemic
    - The Creole Controversy/The Angela Show, 1990/1; Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 45)
      Program aired on WYES, Channel 12 about the definition of Creole people in Louisiana (1990 - 30mins) and an episode of 'The Angela Show', WWL New Orleans TV station, 1991.
    - St Augustine High School, New Orleans, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 200, Folder 46)
      Making a Difference, A Beacon of Hope, Super Bowl Show and National Geographic Brass Bands
    - Sunday Morning News - NEA, 1992; Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 47)
      EP-92-2965 (04/12/1992)
    - Rocking the Nation for Education, 1991; Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 200, Folder 48)
      Press Conference 09/26/1991
    - Photographs (Box 201)
      Color Adjustment and BIBA: Photographic Negs, contact sheets and production photos
    - Photographs (Box 202)
      BIBA: Photographic Negs, contact sheets and production photos
    - Photographic slides (Box 203)
      BIBA: Production Slides
    - Tribute to Marlon Riggs Sampler, 1994; Video: S-VHS; 60mins (Box 232, Folder 49)
      Newark Black Film Fest 07 Jul 1994
    - Photographs, 1991 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      Photograph of Riggs taken by Dutch Photographer Frits de Ridder, 11/28/1991
    - Photographs (Box 239, Folder 2)
      Photographs of Riggs, friends and family, unknown visit, 1970s/80s
    - Photographs (Box 239, Folder 3)
      Identification cards/photographs Riggs, 1970s
    - Photographs (Box 239, Folder 4)
      Photographic negs and prints of CORE picketlines, 1964
    - Photographs (Box 239, Folder 5)
      Photographic negs of Mrs Medgar Evers reception, NYC, 1963
    - Photographs (Box 239, Folder 6)
      Photographic negs of NYC marches, pickets and vigils, 1962/3
    - Photographs (Box 239, Folder 7)
      Photographic negs of NYC marches, pickets and vigils, 1963-5
- Series 3: Other Papers
  This series contains paper materials that could not be directly related to film projects and are divided into subseries of research, writings, correspondence, personal items and financial papers.
  Subseries are divided as follows: Subseries 1: Paper materials relating to Research materials, Subseries 2: Writings (either about Riggs or by Riggs), includes Journalism papers, Subseries 3: Paper materials relating to business correspondence, Subseries 4 - Paper materials relating to personal correspondence such as letters, cards, notebooks and diaries, Subseries 5 - Paper materials relating to financial matters, both business and personal
  Subseries 1 consists of newsletters and newspaper articles that were of interest to Riggs for either personal or professional reasons and contain subjects as varied as AIDS, relationships between black and white men, gay networks, California local interests, public broadcasting, censorship in the media, race and black history.
  Subseries 2 contains newsletters, newspapers, magazines and articles written about or containing interviews with Riggs, or written/presented by him and published in various formats. This subseries also contains papers from his own time on the Graduate Journalism course as well as from his days of teaching the course.
  Subseries 3 relates to correspondence with individuals and institutions and organizations on a professional basis. Subjects include details of conferences attended and presented at, PBS committees and meetings, media organizations and film and arts institutes. Correspondence names include Phillip Brooks, Eric Connell, Chuck Cummings, Brian Freeman, Henry Louis Gates Jnr, Thomas Harris, Lyle Harris, Ron Simmons, Bill T. Jones, Isaac Julien, Assotto Saint, Ron Simmons, Andre Reeder, Donald Woods, Michael Franti and Essex Hemphill
  Subseries 4 contains personal correspondence such as letters, cards, notebooks, diaries, and photographs. There is a box of material items including a tshirt worn by Riggs and a backdrop used in film productions. Notebooks and diaries cover the 1980s. Correspondance covers personal letters and cards sent to Riggs in the 1980s from family and friends.
  Subseries 5 consists of financial records relating either to film projects or personal finances. The majority of personal financial information covering bank statements, receipts, checks and credit card information was returned to the donators as sensitive material. Retained financial records that have been kept to show examples of record keeping in the organization have restricted access. Other items include funding bids and proposals, invoices and receipts, expense accounts, payroll accounts, and some tax records.